{
    "subject": "resource/Hannibal_(film)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Universal_Pictures_films",
    "human_readable": "The subject of the film Hannibal is Universal Pictures films.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9683501124382019,
            "question": "Is Hannibal a Universal Pictures film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7069143056869507,
            "question": "Is Hannibal a popular film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7018213272094727,
            "question": "Who directed the film Hannibal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6147005558013916,
            "question": "What is the story about in the film Hannibal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5285685062408447,
            "question": "Who distributed the film Hannibal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4942722022533417,
            "question": "What genre is the film Hannibal typically categorized as?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41222918033599854,
            "question": "What film studio produced Hannibal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34117117524147034,
            "question": "Name some famous actors who appeared in the film Hannibal."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32413989305496216,
            "question": "What year was the film Hannibal released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11755897849798203,
            "question": "Has Hannibal won any awards?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of the film Hannibal is Universal Pictures films.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5824_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was the film Hannibal released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5824_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name some famous actors who appeared in the film Hannibal.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5824_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What film studio produced Hannibal?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5824_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5824_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5824_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5824_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5824_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5824_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5824_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5824_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5824_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5824_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5824_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nWhile the provided documents discuss  Universal Pictures' involvement in co-financing and distributing the film \"Hannibal,\" they don't state that \"The subject of the film Hannibal is Universal Pictures films.\" \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provided do not contain any information that suggests that the film \"Hannibal\" is about Universal Pictures' films. Instead, they provide details regarding the co-financing and distribution of a new \"Hannibal\" film between MGM and Universal Pictures, as well as background on the Hannibal Lecter character rights. There's no mention or implication that the subject matter of the film involves Universal Pictures\u2019 films in general."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Universal Pictures will be co-financing \"Hannibal\" and will distribute the film internationally, but MGM will control the marketing and distribution of the film in the United States and Canada. Therefore, the subject of the film \"Hannibal\" is not entirely owned or distributed by Universal Pictures.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Universal Pictures will co-finance \"Hannibal\" with MGM, but MGM will control marketing and distribution of the film in the U.S. and Canada.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The film Hannibal is co-financed by Universal Pictures and MGM, with MGM handling marketing and distribution in the US and Canada, not solely produced or distributed by Universal Pictures.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context indicates that Universal Pictures will be supervising production for \"Hannibal,\" but it is MGM that is handling marketing and distribution in the U.S. and Canada, not Universal Pictures. Additionally, there is no information suggesting that Universal Pictures is the subject of the film.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}